http://www.barcodefactory.com/solutions/privacy

Home » Solutions »
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy
Paragon Print Systems, Inc. Privacy Policy
At Paragon Print Systems, Inc. we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders only. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. How does Paragon Print Systems, Inc. protect customer information? When you place orders or access your account information, we use a secure server. The secure server software, (Transport Layer Security or "TLS"), encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
How does Paragon Print Systems, Inc., protect customer information? When you place orders or access your account information, we use secure servers. We also employ a professional Security Company to monitor our efforts for stat-of-the
art safety. The secure server software (Using Secure Socket Layer, or "SSL") encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
Let's stay in touch
Paragon Print Systems, Inc. sends a weekly information e-mail from BarcodeFactory.com to help you keep up with technology changes, rebates, trade-ins and special offers to our customer list. Add us to your white-list by sending us
your email here.
We do NOT share our customer e-mail list with any other company. E-mails are protected by multiple layers of security.
For more information or to enroll, please fill out the form or call us at 888-237-8525.
Support
Privacy Policy
More Questions?
